# Puneeth N

Bangalore Urban district, India



puneethnviraat@gmail.com



8970585459



linkedin.com/in/puneeth-n-796630ab

# **Summary**

I have 3+ years of hands-on experience Efficiently on coding websites and applications using modern HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Building state of the art, easy to use, user-friendly websites and applications is truly a passion of mine. In addition to my knowledge base, I actively seek out new technologies and stay up-to-date on industry trends and advancements. This has allowed me to stay ahead of the curve and deliver exceptional work to all of my employers, including those I've worked for on a project basis.

# **Experience**

#### Senior Web Developer

Unilog

Nov 2021 - Present (2 years 7 months)

### Senior Software Engineering

Wipro

Dec 2020 - Nov 2021 (1 year)

Versatile Front-end Developer with 3+ years of experience designing, developing, and managing complex web sites and applications. Specializes in Angular and responsive design.

# **@** Frontend Developer

Globals Inc.

Apr 2019 - Jul 2020 (1 year 4 months)

### Frontend Web Developer

ChanRe Rheumatology & Immunology Center & Research

Apr 2017 - Apr 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Working as a frontend developer.

#### **Education**



#### Visvesvaraya Technological University

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.), Electrical, Electronics and Communications

Engineering

2010 - 2016

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp

# Skills

React.js • HTML5 • JavaScript • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • jQuery • node.js • mongoDB • GitHub • SASS